Edgar F. Schilder Papers
Edgar F. Schilder Papers
- Photographs
  - International Newsreel and Syracuse Post Standard photographs, undated; 27 items; parts cut from larger photographs (Box 4)
students B2F7 B3F2 B6F5 B7F5 B7F10-B7F11
Supreme Court B1F6 B6F6
Syracuse B1F1-B1F3 B1F6 B1F8-B1F9 B2F1 B5F5 B5F7 B6F3-B6F4 B6F6-B7F3 B7F6 B7F8-B7F9 B10F1 B10F3 B10F6-B10F7 B11F5
Syracuse China B10F8
Syracuse Post-Standard B1F7 B10F3
Syracuse University B1F2 B6F4
Syracuse University football B1F1 B1F3-B1F6 B1F8-B2F1 B8F2 B10F1-B10F2 B10F5 B11F2
Syracuse, downtown B1F3-B1F4 B2F5 B10F6-B10F7
Taft Hartley Act B7F6
taxes B1F4-B1F7 B1F9-B1F10 B2F3-B3F5 B4F2-B4F5 B4F7-B5F3 B5F6 B5F8 B6F2-B7F7 B7F9-B8F2 B9F1 B10F2 B10F4-B10F7 B10F9-B11F1 B11F5
teachers B6F4
Texas B5F3
Tojo, Hideki B5F6
transportation B1F1 B1F6-B1F9 B5F3 B5F5 B5F7 B6F5 B7F6 B7F8 B7F10 B10F1-B10F2 B10F5 B10F7 B11F5
Truman, Harry S. B6F2 B6F6 B7F5-B7F9 B10F2 B10F4 B10F8
Tunisia B3F4-B3F5
Turkey B2F5 B4F1-B4F2 B4F7
U.S. Census B8F2
Ukraine B4F7
unions B5F7
United Nations B3F1-B3F2 B3F5-B4F2 B6F1 B6F3 B8F3 B9F2
United War Fund B4F7 B5F7-B5F8
vacation B1F2-B1F3 B1F5 B1F9 B2F6 B2F8 B3F4 B4F5 B5F7-B6F1 B6F3 B6F5 B6F7-B7F2 B9F1 B10F3-B10F4 B10F8-B10F10 B11F2 B11F4
victory gardens B3F3-B4F3 B4F7-B5F1 B5F4-B5F5 B5F7 B6F1-B6F2 B7F9 B9F1
voting B5F8 B7F2 B10F4 B11F3
Vyacheslav, Molotov B10F8
war bonds B2F8-B3F1 B3F4 B4F4-B4F5 B4F7-B5F1 B5F3-B5F4 B5F7 B6F1 B7F8 B9F1
war debt B2F1
weather B1F1 B1F5-B1F9 B2F2 B2F5-B2F6 B4F1 B4F3-B4F4 B5F5 B6F2 B6F5 B6F7-B7F1 B7F4-B7F8 B10F1 B10F4 B10F6-B10F7 B11F2
welfare B10F2
Wilkie, Wendell B7F10
winter B1F1-B1F2 B1F4 B1F6 B1F8-B1F9 B2F1-B2F2 B2F4-B2F6 B2F9 B3F2 B3F5 B4F2-B4F5 B4F7 B5F2-B6F2 B6F5-B7F3 B7F6-B7F7 B7F9 B7F11-B8F1 B9F1 B10F2 B10F4-B10F5 B10F7 B10F9-B11F5
women B5F3 B5F5 B6F6 B11F2 B11F4-B11F5
World War I B7F10 B11F6
World War II B2F5 B2F8-B4F5 B4F7-B5F6 B6F2 B7F8-B7F10 B8F2-B9F2 B10F4-B10F5 B10F7 B10F9-B10F10
Yugoslavia B10F1